好啊 迪恩 我是莉莉丝
Hi,dean. it's me, Lilith.
你不是真的莉莉丝
You are not real!
你怎么了 迪恩
What's the matter,dean?
难道你忘了在这里的欢乐时光吗
Don't you remember all the fun you had down there?
救命啊
Somebody help me!
又见到你了 迪恩
Hello again,dean.
不记得我了吗
Don't you recognize me? ugh!
我们在地狱里可走的挺近的
But we were so close... in hell.
阿拉斯泰尔
Alastair.
他们用各种方式将我扒皮
They sliced...
钻心
Carved...
拆骨直到
And tore at me in ways that you...
阿拉斯泰尔给我开出了离开邢台的条件是
And alastair would make me an offer to
让我去折磨那些被禁锢的灵魂
Take me off the rack if I started the torturing.
而每一天  我都告诉他我会坚持到新生
And every day,i told him to stick it where the sun shines.
整整30年来  我都这样跟他说
For 30 years,I told him.
但我无法再忍受了 萨姆
Then I couldn't do it anymore,sammy.
之后我离开了那个行刑台
And I got off that rack.
而我则开始折磨它们
And I started ripping them apart.
我都不记得了我折磨过多少灵魂
I lost count of how many souls.
不是吧
Aw,come on.
我靠
Ohh,crap.
见鬼了吧
What the hell?!
是你
You?
这不可能
I-it's impossible.
离我远点
You stay away from me!
[邪恶力量 第4季11集]
你在干嘛
What are you doing?
你觉得我是在干嘛
What's it look like I'm doing?
像是在找工作
Like you're looking for a job.
那像是掷骰子的游戏
Yahtzee.
我们2个小时前刚干完活
We just finished a job like two hours ago.
肾上腺素还在分泌我猜
Adrenaline's still pumping,I guess.
你怎么说
So,what do you think...
锡达拉皮兹 塔尔萨还是芝加哥
Cedar rapids,tulsa,or chi-town?
我把所有的力气都用在这事上 我说的是真的
I am all for working. I really am.
不过你带着咱俩马不停蹄的猎杀快1个月了
But you got us chasing cases nonstop for like a month now.
-我们得睡觉 -等我们死了就可以睡了
We need sleep. ah,we can sleep when we're dead.
你已经精疲力竭了 迪恩
You're exhausted,dean.
-我很好 -不 才不是
I'm good. no,you're not.
你带着怒气在猎杀 但你不能一辈子这样下去
You're running on fumes,and you can't run forever.
我带着什么在猎杀恶魔
And what am I running from?
带着你告诉我的那些事
From what you told me.
还是我们在假装那些事从没发生过
Or are we pretending that never happened?
内布拉斯加州 斯坦顿 一个农场小镇
Stratton,nebraska -- farm town.
一男子被砍死在一个大门和房间都上锁的屋子里
A man gets hacked to death in a locked room inside a locked house.
没有侵入的迹象
No signs of forced entry.
听起来想鬼魂
Sounds like a ghost.
当然是
Yes,it does.
3个卧室 2个浴室外加1个杀人犯
Boy,three bedrooms,two baths,and one homicide.
这地方和蛋糕一样受欢迎
This place is gonna sell like hotcakes.
来看看这里
Hey,check this out.
可能是小型升降机
It's probably a dumbwaiter.
大多数老房子都有这玩意儿
All these old houses had them.
真是无所不知啊
Know-it-all.
什么?
What?
你说..
You said...
我说什么了
What?
没什么
Never mind.
没有血迹,刚上的墙面漆 挺不错的
Well,no bloodstains,fresh coat of paint,this is a bunch of bubkes.
这插满了针
Needle's all over the place.
是电线
Yeah -- power lines.
很好
Great.
那么...
So,uh...
这是最烦人的
Well,that's super-disturbing.
难不成在这地方弄完之后留下的
Think it got left behind?
谁会这么干
By who?
除非比尔 吉布森喜欢玩娃娃头
Unless bill gibson likes to play with doll heads.
我想你说过这地方还在出售中
I thought you said this place was still for sale.
显然不是了
Apparently,it's not.
来啊 巴斯特
Come on,buster!
觉得怎么样 很漂亮不是么
What do you think? it's nice,right?
谁在我们来之前会无聊的来这里看房
Did anyone bother to check if we get a signal out here?
是我 凯特
Actually,i did,kate.
总之我们决定搬家的时候就已经毁了你的一生了
But we decided to move anyway,just to ruin your life.
来吧
Come on.
把行李卸下来
Let's unpack.
泰德叔叔 把我的放这里就行了
Uncle ted,please back me up here.
孩子是对的 布莱恩 你毁了她的一切
Kid's right,bri. you're ruining her life.
看到了吧
See?
多谢 泰德叔叔
Thanks for the help,une ted.
我只是说了大实话 伙计
I call it like I see it,buddy.
怎么了?
What?
很棒
Be nice.
我当然棒
I am nice.
觉得怎么样
What do you think?
干的还不错吧
We do okay?
我可不知道
I don't know.
他们是谁
Who are they?
我能帮上什么忙么
Can I help you?
你是新的房主
Hi. are you the new owner?
是的 你们是...
Yeah. you guys are...?
这位是斯坦威先生 我是巴巴尔先生
This is mr. stanwyk. I'm mr. babar.
城镇执行处的
County code enforcement.
这房子我们已经检查过了
We had the building inspected last week.
有问题吗
Is there a problem?
的确有点小问题 我们在墙壁内侧发现了石棉会导致漏气
Asbestos in the walls,a gas leak -- yeah,i'd say we got a problem.
石棉 什么意思
Asbestos? meaning what?
直到我们确定没有问题 否则这里不能住
Meaning until this house is up to code,it's uninhabitable.
你在说我们不能住这儿
You're saying we can't stay here?
会有健康危害 我想你不会希望看到
It's a health hazard. you don't want to.
等等 我们刚开了400英里的车来这里
Hold up. we just drove 400 miles.
这条路往下开就是汽车旅馆
There's a motel just down the road.
挺干净的 我建议住那里
Till this gets cleaned up,I suggest you stay there.
好吧 如果不同意呢
All right,and what if we don't?
你会吃到罚单并坐牢
Well,you get a fine,you go to jail.
后果自负
Pick your poison.
就一晚
One night.
就一晚 我会尽快解决这一切 我保证
One night,and I'll take care of everything,a.s.a.p. -- I promise.
做的好
Yeah,you do that.
又是汽车旅馆
Another motel?
真是好极了  老爸
Awesome,dad.
我希望这家也会有妓女清单  就像昨晚那家一样
I hope this one has hooker sheets,like the last one.
凯特
Kate.
上车了  丹尼
Come on,danny!
当你发现时房子里的情况是什么样  凯瑞太太
What did the room look like when you found it,mrs. curry?
我已经和当地的警察说过了  那儿有血
I already told the local boys -- there was blood...
到处都是
Everywhere.
那吉布森先生  他的尸体在哪儿
And mr. gibson -- where was he?
到处都是
Everywhere.
你花了多少时间才将吉布森先生的屋子打扫干净
How long have you been cleaning mr. gibson's house?
大概五年左右
Mm. about five years.
这么说你应该非常了解他
So you knew him pretty well.
不能算非常  他完全过着与世隔绝的生活
Oh,not really well. he was real private.
但生活却一点都不简单
Not the easiest man.
我不是在责备他
Not that I blame him.
你的意思是
What do you mean?
他妻子在分娩时过世了
His wife dies in childbirth.
20年后  女儿又在阁楼上上吊自杀
Daughter hangs herself in the attic 20 years later.
我都觉得难以接受
I'd be bitter,too.
我想我留了些照片
I think I got some pictures.
给
Here.
谢谢
Thanks.
可以给我们吗
Can we keep these?
没问题
Suit yourself.
那个女儿为什么要自杀呢
Now,why'd the daughter kill herself?
我不清楚  那是在我来之前的事了
I don't know. that was before my time.
你在打扫时有没有发现什么奇怪的东西吗
Did you ever notice anything odd in the house when you were cleaning it?
比如说呢
Like what?
比如  像灯会忽闪忽闪
Like,you know,like lights going on and off,
东西会移位
Things not being where you left them.
都没有
No.
不过  到是有一件事
Well,maybe there was one thing.
什么事
What's that?
有时候  我觉得我听到
Well,sometimes,I thought I heard like a...
墙里面的沙沙声
Rustling in the walls.
-像有只老鼠  -是的
- Like a rat? - yeah.
说不定是某些小王八羔子在外面恶作剧呢
Must have been some big sons of guns out there,huh?
不知道  一个人影都没见到过
Wouldn't know. never saw any.
你知道
Do you happen to know
吉布森太太和她女儿被埋葬在哪里吗
where mrs. gibson and her daughter were buried?
他们都是火葬的
Ah,they were both cremated.
好了
All right.
看来这不可能和妈妈或是女儿有关
So it probably wasn't the mom or the daughter.
那个鬼究竟是谁
Whose ghost was it?
不知道
I don't know.
不过我知道我们需要回到那儿进行一次彻底的调查
But I say we give that place a real once-over and see.
强制规定  一派胡言  根本就没有石棉
Code enforcement,my ass. there's no asbestos.
-你确定  -是的
- You sure? - hell yes.
我修过那么多房子绝对可以肯定了
I've built enough homes to know that.
根本就没有煤气泄漏
No gas leak,either.
那那两个家伙是谁
Who were those guys?
绝不是乡下的人  这是我唯一可以肯定的
Not from the county -- I can tell you that.
你没事吧
You okay?
当然  当然
Yeah. Yeah.
我只是觉得我刚才看到了什么  就是这样
I just thought I saw something,that's all.
在  在这儿一切都会好起来的  凯特
It -- it's gonna be great here,kate.
真的
It really is.
当然  妈妈
Yeah,mom.
我相信
I'm sure.
所有都会变的
Everything's gonna change.
丹尼  你在收拾你的东西吗
Danny! are you unpacking?
是的 我就快收拾好了
Uh,yeah. I'm almost finished.
你好
Hello?
没关系的
It's okay.
我是丹尼
I'm danny.
南瓜很易种植  但种植甜菜就需要酸度较大的土壤
"zucchini will grow,but the soil is too acidic for beets."
你懂这些吗
Do you understand any of this?
你有闻到那味道吗
Can you smell that?
那味道
That.
闻起来就像是有一只浣熊或是什么东西死在那里面一样
It smells like a raccoon died up there or something.
那很幽默  谢谢
That's pleasant. thank you.
我可以继续我刚才的自言自语吗
Can I continue having a conversation with myself?
嘿  我在听呢
Well,i'm listening.
一个...蔬菜园
A...vegetable garden.
我们这是在干嘛 布莱恩
What are we doing,bri?
什么意思
What do you mean?
我们  在一个农场
Us...on a farm...
讨论南瓜
Talking about zucchini.
这里将来一定会不一样的
It's gonna be different.
我向你保证
I promise you.
我们一定会很幸福的
We're gonna be happy.
但是如果没有呢
And if we're not?
一定会
We will be.
必须幸福
We have to be.
我不能让孩子们再重蹈去年的覆辙
I can't put the kids through another year like the last.
真胡来
Crap.
现在该做什么
So,what now?
我们可以直接告诉他们事实的真相
We could tell them the truth.
真的吗
Really?
不  不是真的
No,not really.
嘿  你们俩  过来看看这个
Hey,guys! you're gonna want to come see this!
这是什么
What the...
蜡笔
Crayon.
丹尼
Danny!
给我乖乖下来
Get your butt down here!
-告诉你  如果是我的孩子这么做  -他不是你的孩子  泰德
- Tell you what,if my kid did this. - he's not your kid,ted.
别管这事
Just butt out.
嘿  别太严厉了
Hey. go easy on him.
他老师说过他也许只是在发泄
The teacher said he might act out.
嘿  小家伙
Hey,buddy.
是不是有事该向我和你妈妈坦白
Something you want to tell me and your mom?
不是我干的
I didn't do that.
好了
Okay.
听着  你只要说实话  然后把它清理干净就行了  明白吗
Look,just tell me the truth,and all you got to do is clean it up,okay?
不会处罚你的
No punishment.
但不是我干的
But I didn't.
是墙里的那个女孩子干的
The girl in the walls did it.
墙里的女孩
The girl in the walls?
她希望你们离开这儿而让我留下来
She wants you to go and me to stay.
行了  最后一次  实话  小家伙
All right,one last time -- the truth,buddy.
那就是实话
That is the truth.
我可以留下来  但是她讨厌大人  如果你们不离开
I can stay,but she hates grown-ups,and if you don't leave,
她真的真的会发狂
She's gonna get really,really mad!
好吧  回房间去
All right,go to your room.
妈妈
Mom!
如果安迪在这儿  他一定信我
If andy were here,he'd believe me!
上楼去  马上
Upstairs -- now!
没事的  巴斯特  没事的
It's okay,buster. it's okay.
我也不喜欢这儿
I hate it here,too.
巴斯特  恶心
Ew,buster! gross!
你怎么了
What's the matter with you?
天呐
Oh,my god.
神啊
Oh,god.
-额哦   -没事
- Ew! ew! - it's okay.
卡蒂  宝贝  宝贝  冷静下来告诉我们怎么回事
Katie,baby,baby. calm down and tell us what happened.
我刚刚被令人毛骨悚然的类似鬼马精灵的鬼骚扰
I just got molested by casper the pervy ghost!
-这就是经过  -鬼
- That's what happened! - ghost?
是的  爸爸  一只鬼
Yes,dad -- a ghost!
是墙里的女孩
It's the girl in the walls!
谁
Who?!
你们两个都给我住嘴
Both of you,knock it off.
我们听见尖叫声  出什么事了
We heard screams. what's going on?
你们两个碰过我女儿了
Oh,you two! did you touch my daughter?!
什么  没有
What? no.
你们俩是谁
Who are you guys?
放轻松点
Relax,please.
你们遇见鬼了
You have a ghost.
鬼
A ghost.
我告诉过你  是个女孩
I told you! it's the girl!
你们俩都放轻松点
Both of you,relax.
你们演的是哪出戏
What are you guys playing?
你们一家都有危险  需要马上离开这房子
Your family's in danger. you need to get out of the house now.
究竟怎么回事
What the hell?
所有人都别动
Nobody move!
巴斯特
Buster!
Buster?
巴斯特  巴斯特
Buster! buster!
什么鬼东西
What the hell?
巴斯特
Buster!
回屋内去
Go back inside.
快去
Go!
我们不是坏人  但你们有危险
We are not the bad guys,but you're in danger.
当务之急
First thing's first.
你带家人离开这儿
You got to get your family out of here.
去我曾说过的汽车旅馆
Head to the motel I was talking about.
在那儿你们会比较安全
You'll be safe there.
你们俩要做什么
What are you two gonna do?
噢不
Oh...
噢  见鬼
Oh,come on!
噢  去死
伙计  枪都不见了
Dude,the guns are gone.
其他的也是
So is the...
基本上  什么都没了
Basically,everything is gone.
卡车也坏了
Truck's no good.
四轮胎都被砍破了
Both tires slashed.
什么样的鬼会搞轮胎啊
What kind of ghost messes with a man's wheels?!
怎么了  出什么事了
What's going on? what's going on?
她在那儿  在那儿
She's there! she's there!
哪里
Where?!
就那儿  灌木丛中
She was right there in the woods!
鬼会在外面干吗
What's a ghost doing outside?
你想留下来查个究竟吗
You want to stay and find out?
所有人都进屋去
Everybody inside.
你疯了吗  我们该离开这个鬼地方
Are you crazy? we need to get the hell out of here!
去哪里  这鬼正在追杀我们
In what?! this ghost is hunting us!
所有人马上进屋  快
Everybody back inside now! move!
无论外面的是什么东西  都跨不进这个圈
Whatever's outside,it can't get in this circle.
只要盐圈不坏  这里就是最安全的地方
As long as the salt line is unbroken,this is the safest place to be.
免于恶鬼的追杀吗
Safe from ghosts?
对  事实就是如此
Yes,as a matter of fact.
好的  我不会再听这鬼话了
Okay. I'm not listening to this anymore.
来吧
Come on.
我要带我家人离开这里  我们走
I got to get my family out of here. let's go.
除非我们杀了这鬼东西不然没人能离开
Nobody's going anywhere until we kill this thing.
先生别这样  我们就是干这行的
Sir,please. this is what we do.
请相信我们
Just...trust us.
你们猎杀鬼
You hunt ghosts?
对的
That's right.
像史酷比
Like scooby-doo?
更厉害点
Better.
你在外面见过她是吧
You saw her outside,right?
好的  是这俩女孩中一个吗
Okay. does she look like either one of these girls?
是她
Her.
她更苍白脏点  但确实是她
She was paler and a lot dirtier,but that was her.
那是墙里的女孩
That's the girl in the walls.
所以是女儿
So it's the daughter?
照片里的女孩  死了吗
That girl in the picture -- she-she's dead?
她在这屋里自杀了
She killed herself inside this house.
为什么女佣要歪曲她的故事呢
So,what -- the maid got her story wrong?
丽贝卡没有被火化吗
Rebecca wasn't cremated?
除非她的思想同屋内的某种东西相联结
Unless her spirit's just attached to something inside the house.
她在顶楼上吊自杀的吗
She hung herself in the attic,right?
你想照看他们吗  我去一探究竟
You want to babysit? I'll check it out.
听着  我不管谁在哪里上吊自杀了
Look -- I don't care who hung themselves where.
-也许正发生着什么  但  -是思想  伙计
- Maybe something is going on here,but -- it's a spirit,man.
不是  只是一些边远地区的乡下贱妇
No,it's just some backwoods hillbilly bitch,
我才不会因此
And I'm not about to sit around here
而坐等她来拯救我的危机
Waiting for her to go all "deliverance" on my ass.
-没人可以离开这房子  -阻止我看看
- Well,nobody's leaving the house. - stop me.
听着  伙计  我有枪
Listen,man. I've got a gun.
不回到圈内
You don't get your ass back in that circle,
就让你身上穿洞
You're gonna have yourself a third hole.
伙计  你没枪
Dude,you don't have a gun.
那又怎样
And?
今晚我不会让那杂种的或其他人死
I'm not letting that bastard or anyone else die tonight.
冷静了没
You cool?
走
Go.
嗨  酷男
Hey. fonzie.
问你个问题
Question for you.
这个用盐围成的不可破坏的力量区域
This indestructible force field made out of salt...
必须是洁净或什么吧
Have to be kosher stuff,or what?
别说了  特德
Knock it off,ted.
那是什么
What was that?
妈妈
Mom.
好吧  所有人保持镇定
All right,everybody stay calm.
她是只鬼  进不到圈子里的
She's a ghost. she can't come in the circle.
你不是说鬼魂不能跨过这个圈吗
I thought you said ghosts couldn't cross the circle.
是不能  所以她不是鬼
They can't. she's not a ghost.
开枪射她  射她
Shoot her! shoot her!
这恐怕
yeah,about that...
快跑  快  快
Go,go,go! move!
你没事吧
Hey. you okay?
-其他人在哪  -藏起来了
- Where is everybody? - hiding.
好吧  把他们找出来  快去
All right,go get them. go. go get them.
那不是鬼
So,it's not a ghost.
-只是个女孩  -不只是个女孩  是疯子内尔
- So,it's just a girl? - it's not just a girl. it's psycho nell.
要我说  绝对是个人
I'm telling you,man -- humans.
那她是谁
So,who is she,then?
不知道  也许是那个女儿  丽贝卡
I don't know. maybe it's the daughter,rebecca.
也许她没上吊自杀
Maybe she didn't hang herself.
不可能  否则她现在都50岁了
Dude,no. she'd have to be like 50 years old by now.
我不清楚  你在阁楼上找到什么没
Well,i don't know. what'd you find in the attic?
基本是些破烂  我找到了丽贝卡的日记
Some old junk. I found rebecca's diary. that's about it.
我还指望你找个榴弹炮来呢
I wish you'd found a howitzer.
听着  我们必须保证这家人的安全
Listen,we got to get this family safe.
那只是个人  这样他们可以逃走
I mean,it's just a human,so they can make a run for it.
我们只要拖住她
We just got to hold her off.
我们没事
We're okay.
丹尼  泰德  我们得走了
Danny! ted! we got to go!
我在儿
I'm good!
丹尼  快出来
Danny! come on!
丹尼  伙计  我们要走了
Danny,buddy,we got to go!
我告诉过你们那是个疯婆娘
Told you it was some crazy bitch.
是  你说了
yes,you did.
到镇上去  我们随后就到
Hey,uh,head to town. we'll take it from here,okay?
丹尼  宝贝  我们要出发了
Danny,come on,baby! we're leaving!
丹尼  要走了
Danny,we got to go!
布莱恩  他  他在哪里
Brian,where -- where is he?
丹尼
Danny!
苏萨  苏萨  苏萨  苏萨
Suse,suse,suse,suse.
我们会找到他的  我保证
We will find danny. I promise you.
不
No!
带上凯特  立刻就走
No,take kate and go now.
马上  趁还有机会
Now! while you still have a chance!
没找到丹尼我不走  绝不
Not without danny! no way!
我不要单独跟妈妈走到外面去
I am not going out there with mom alone!
她说的没错  她是对的
She's right. she's right.
在我们找到你们儿子前
Until we find your son
车棚是最安全的地方
the safest place for you right now is in the shed.
我也不去那里
I am not going in there,either.
你必须去
Yes,you are.
那里最安全
It is the best defense.
窗都封死了  而且只有一个门
The windows are boarded up. it's got one door.
那儿是我们目前最好的选择
It's our best shot right now.
相信我
Trust me.
苏萨  凯特  走吧
Suse,kate...go.
快去
Go.
好吧
All right.
你跟我看着外面
You and me will take the outside.
你们两去屋里
You two take the house.
走吧
Let's go.
你在干嘛
What are you doing?
她是人  肯定要有个住处
She's human. she had to come from somewhere.
你受得了这味儿
You smell that?
习惯了
Every day.
跟上
Come on.
你不能下去
You're not going down there.
那你下去
Well,do you want to?
千万别拽我的脚  千万别拽我的脚
Please nobody grab my leg. please nobody grab my leg.
狗  晚餐吃的
Dog -- it's what's for dinner.
丹尼
Danny?
找到什么了吗
Find anything?
找到了  她的厨房
Yeah -- her kitchen.
她的什么
Her what?
我们为什么要一直傻站在这儿
Look...why are we just standing here?
我们进去吧  检查下房子
Let's go in. let's check the house.
我们必须在这里等他们回来  明白吗
We have to wait for those guys to get back,okay?
萨姆  是我  让我进去
Sam,it's me. help me out.
你们找到丹尼了吗
Did you get danny?
没有
No.
没找到
No?
那泰德在哪
W-well,where's ted?
在外面
He's outside.
为什么他不进来
Well,why doesn't he come inside?
因为我还得把他带出去
Because I had to carry him out.
对不起
I'm sorry.
那是  那是什么意思
What does -- what does that mean?
你说对不起是什么意思
What does that mean that you're sorry?
你是说他死了吗
Are you saying that he's dead?
不  他没说他死了
No. he's not saying that he's dead.
你不是这个意思  对吗
You're not saying that,are you?
我们在墙里  然后她袭击我们
We were in the walls,and she attacked.
我没能及时救到他
And I couldn't get to him in time.
泰德叔叔死了
Uncle ted is dead?
我不该让他单独留下的
I shouldn't have left him alone.
我真的很抱歉
I'm very sorry.
我们会找到他的  苏萨  一定会的
We'll find him,suse. we will.
还有哪里没查过
Where else is there to look?
丹尼死了  对不对
Danny's dead,isn't he?
-不  苏萨  -为什么不会
- No,suse. - why not?
她杀了我弟弟  现在又杀了我儿子
She killed my brother,now she killed my son.
不  丹尼还活着
No,danny is alive.
不  不  他死了
No. no,he isn't.
不  他活着
Yes,he is.
你还记得他说的
Do you remember what he said
住在墙里的女孩吗
about the girl who lived in the walls?
她说他可以留着
She said he could stay.
不
No.
我就是不懂为什么我们要受这种罪
I just don't understand why this happens to us.
我们是好人  是很好的一家人
I mean,we're good people. we're a good family.
安迪的事已经发生了
What happened to andy happened,okay?
我对它无能为力
I cannot change that.
但我会找到丹尼的  我保证
But I will find danny. I promise you.
我找到他之后  一切就都会好了
And when I do,we are gonna be fine.
你和我  还有孩子们  我们都会没事的
You and me,the kids -- we're gonna be fine.
安迪是你儿子
Andy your son?
长子
Oldest.
他去年出车祸死了
He got himself killed in a car accident last year.
我很遗憾
I'm sorry.
我和苏萨差点为此崩溃
Nearly tore suse and I apart.
而且恐怕现在还没缓过来
Still could,i imagine.
所以我们搬到这里来
That's why we moved here.
新的环境  新的开始
Fresh air,fresh start.
甚至不是我说的
Not even my line.
婚姻顾问
Marriage counselor.
或许她说的对
Or she might be right.
毕竟  在乡下  没什么是过不去的
After all,what could possibly go wrong in the country?
我会把你的儿子找回来
I'm getting your son back.
如果这是我能做的最后一件善事
If it's the last godforsaken thing I do.
你为什么这么在意
Why do you care so much?
迪恩
Dean.
我有事要跟你说
We got to talk.
那是什么
What is that?
丽贝卡的日记  我刚读完它
Rebecca's diary. I just finished reading it.
然后呢
And?
在那后面的女孩
That girl back there --
我敢肯定她是丽贝卡的女儿
I'm pretty sure she was Rebecca's daughter.
丽贝卡有个小孩
Rebecca had a kid?
她说的都是这个   怀孕了
It's all she talks about -- being pregnant,
因怀孕而感到羞耻
Being ashamed of being pregnant.
天啊  让"朱诺"（婚神星）搞定它吧
Geez. rent "Juno" get over it.
等等  为什么孩子出生后她还要自杀
Wait -- why kill herself after the baby?
或许因为他爸爸叫她肮脏的小妓女
Maybe because her dad called her a dirty little whore and
还说他要把那小孩锁起来
Said he was gonna lock the baby up
不让任何人看见
where nobody could ever see it.
他会什么要那样说
Why would he say that?
那孩子也是他的
Oh,gross.
对了
Yeah.
也就说  爸爸是孩子的爸爸
So the daddy was the baby-daddy,too?
这家伙是个混球  迪恩
Dude was a monster,Dean.
听起来像奥地利的新闻故事
A story ripped from austrian headlines.
这可是人  兄弟
Humans,man.
她一生都被锁在这栋房子里
So she's been locked up in this house her whole life?
你看过她的眼睛
You saw her eyes.
她有看过光吗  不能说是人类了
Has she ever seen light? she's barely human.
好  那是什么呢
Okay,so,what,then?
她像动物一样被关了起来
She's kept caged up like an animal,
然后她冲了出来  杀了她爸爸
And then she busts out and ganks dear dad,
老爸  爷爷
Old dad/granddad?
我想
I guess.
不能说我会怪她
Well,can't say I blame her.
我敢肯定她的生活就像地狱  迪恩
I'm sure her life was hell,Dean.
那也不能说明她可以随意杀人
That doesn't mean she gets a free pass for a murder spree.
好像你知道地狱是怎么样的
Like you know what hell's like.
我没有
I didn't...
算了吧
Forget it.
那我们在哪可以找到她
So,where do we find her?
孩子总归要吃  对吧
Kid's got to eat,right?
什么
What?
他把她藏起来  并锁了起来
He kept her hidden,locked up...
但他总要给她吃的  不是吗
But he had to feed her,didn't he?
是吧
I guess.
我想我知道在哪
I think I know where.
他本来可以把她藏在下面好几年
He could have kept her hidden down here for years.
给她吃的  没人会知道这事
Kept her fed. nobody would ever know.
丹尼
Danny!
丹尼  小心  我下去
Danny! watch out. I'm going down.
-不  是我儿子  -我知道
-No,that's my son.  -I know it is.
但我说过我会找到他
But I said that I would get him.
我说到做到
I will. let me.
你有窗帘布吗
You got curtains?
我们需要绳子
We need rope.
没事的
It's okay.
孩子  没事的
It's okay,baby.
这婊子简直有鹰爪
Bitch is a klepto.
丹尼
Danny!
你的爸爸就在上面  过来
Your dad's upstairs. come on.
好的
Okay.
小心头  小心你的头
Watch your head. watch your head.
快点  他快回来了
Hurry! he's coming back!
"他"
"He"?
她弟弟
Her brother!
丹尼
Danny!
好了
Okay!
快点  兄弟
Come on,buddy.
快点啊 兄弟
丹尼  别回头看  也别往下看
Don't look back,danny. just don't look down.
妈妈
Mom!
Aah! mom!
快  我抓住你了
Come on. I got you.
你还好吗
You okay?
没事
It's okay.
带他离开这里  你们赶紧走
Get him out of here. you got to go.
迪恩
Dean?
妈妈
Mom!
不
Aah! no!
妈妈
Mom!
苏丝
Suse!
谢谢你们的配合
Thanks for the head start.
让我奇怪的是  你们俩竟然不是警察
Why doesn't it surprise me，you guys don't like the police?
类似于...  相互欣赏之类的吧  真的
Sort of a,uh... mutual-appreciation thing,really.
谢谢了
Well...thank you.
谢谢
Thank you.
你们还好吗
You okay?
不  正好相反
No. we're the opposite of okay.
但...
But...
至少我们在一起
We're together.
你怎么了
You okay?
你知道吗  我觉得这些狗娘养的全都要下地狱
You know,I felt for those sons of bitches back there.
终生的折磨会让你变成像那样的东西
Lifelong torture turns you into something like that.
你进过地狱的  迪恩
You were in hell,dean.
听着  或许你在下面做了不该做的事
Look,maybe you did what you did there...
但你不像他们
But you're not them.
他们不能算是人了
They were barely human.
你说对了
Well,you're right.
我不像他们
I wasn't like them.
我比他们更坏
I was worse.
他们只是动物  山姆  只想捍卫自己的地方
They were animals,Sam,defending territory.
而我...
Me...
我却是在享受
I did it for the sheer pleasure of it.
什么
What?
山姆 我喜欢那样做
I enjoyed it,sam.
他们把我从架子放下来  然后我折磨那些灵魂
They took me off the rack,and I tortured souls,
并且还很享受
and I liked it.
这么多年来...
All those years...
所有的痛苦...
All that pain...
终于让你自己也尝到了
Finally getting to deal some out yourself.
我甚至不关心他们把谁放在我的面前
I didn't care who they put in front of me.
我感受到的痛苦..
That pain I felt...
慢慢地消失了
It just slipped away.
不管我救了多少人...
No matter how many people I save...
也改变不了那样的事实
I can't change that.
根本不能弥补
I can't fill this hole.
永远不能
Not ever.